# ADAM REED

Phone: (936)-581-9609 | Email: <u>adamreedb@gmail.com</u> | Bryan, TX, 77801

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/adam-reed1/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/adam-reed1/</a>

Portfolio: <a href="https://ouchkick.github.io/AdamsPortfolio/">https://ouchkick.github.io/AdamsPortfolio/</a> | GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/OuchKick">https://github.com/OuchKick</a>

### SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer leveraging customer service and finance background to create a more engaging and friendly experience on the web. Recently earning a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of Texas at Austin coding bootcamp, with newly developed skills in responsive web design; with each project to engage the audience for an enjoyable user experience. Ability to work independently and collaboratively to develop multiple projects that greatly increase understanding and interest in web development. Excited to leverage skills as part of a fast-paced, quality-driven field to build better experiences on the web.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, SQL, NoSQL, three.js

**Applications:** GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL

Tools: Express, React, Node, Handlebars, Bootstrap, Spline

#### **Projects**

### Dalila

https://github.com/pigodidog/Dalila http://dalila-app.herokuapp.com/

- A music playlist suggestion application with a lot of easter eggs.
- Focused primarily on using Spline and Bootstrap for the Front-End and some logic structure for the quiz. Had a lot of fun with the little details.
- React, Redux, axios, MongoDB Atlas, Spline, SpotifyAPI.

### **PokéFyte**

https://github.com/Dylan-Casanova/PokeFyte-The-Game https://pokyfyte.herokuapp.com/

- This application allows users to select a Pokémon and fight a variety of other Pokémon in a battle. There is also a Pokédex that provides stats.
- Refactored code from a Pokémon game to work with the application and created a fully developed ReadMe.
- Handlebars, Javascript, CSS, axios, Sequelize.

### **TangibleTunes**

https://github.com/mattjb97/Tangible-Tunes https://mattjb97.github.io/Tangible-Tunes/

- A User can enter the name of a song and the lyrics and corresponding video will populate on the page.
- Responsible for the HTML and also helped with traversing the API calls to get correct lyrics.
- HTML, CSS, Javascript.

### EXPERIENCE

# **Computershare / Senior Customer Service Representative**

2018-2021

College Station, TX

- Facilitated the transfer and sales of securities.
- Assembled up-to-date information on dividend schedules, proxy votes and odd-lot programs.
- Educated employees on details of ESPP (Employee Stock Purchase Plan) and Stock Options from different companies such as Home Depot and Leidos.
- Resolved issues for shareholders.

### Key Accomplishments:

- Succeeded in transition from temporary employee to company employee in under 1 year.
- Consistent recognition for efficiency and quality assurance scores.

### Pizza Hut / Delivery Driver

2016-2018

College Station, TX

- Communicated customer complaints, requests and feedback to company management for swift resolution.
- Preparation of side dishes prior to opening.
- Updated dispatchers frequently to convey changes such as route issues or weather delays potentially impacting deliveries.

### Salata / Kitchen Prep

2014-2014

College Station, TX

- Prepared cooking supplies, ingredients and workstations during opening and closing procedures to maximize efficiency.
- Prepared and expedited food orders to support waitstaff and other team members.
- Practiced proper safety and sanitation standards.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Certificate, Fullstack Web Development – University of Texas Bootcamp

Austin, TX

March 2021 - June 2021

A 12-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

# Associates of Arts, Liberal Arts – Blinn College

College Station, TX

August 2014 - December 2018